B2.
Amy and Daniel are talking about how to stay safe in emergencies.
Listen to their conversation and complete the notes below.
There was some really good advice in that talk.
But what about emergencies?
What should we do if we get caught in an emergency?
Well, if your building is on fire, try to get out as soon as possible.
Cover your mouth and nose with a wet piece of cloth to protect yourself from thick smoke and stay low to the ground.
If it is impossible for you to get out, find a safe place to stay and wait for help.
Yes, and don't go back into a building on fire.
It's very dangerous.
Yes, that's really important.
And car accidents happen every day, so what should we do if we see one?
I think we should make an emergency call as soon as possible.
Then we can check if people in the cars are fine or not.
Remember not to move them if they are badly hurt.
That's useful advice.
I think it's also important to put emergency signs around the cars or other accidents might happen.